Mary van Kleeck Papers, 1849-1998
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES V. ORGANIZATION AND CONFERENCE FILES 1897-1961
  - National Lawyers' Guild 1957 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - National League of Women Voters, [see League of Women Voters] (Box 83)
  - National Peace Conference 1937, [see also SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES-Peace] (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - National Research Council
    - General 1923-25, undated (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Division of Anthropology and Psychology 1924-25 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Scientific Problems of Human Migration
      - Committee on Immigration and Naturalization (House of RepresentativesNov. 1922) (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Conferences 1922-25 (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence (Box 83)
        - General 1923-26 (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
        - Abbott, Edith 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 3)
        - Merriam, Charles Edward 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 4)
        - Mitchell, Wesley C. 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 5)
        - Yerkes, Robert M. 1924-38 (Box 84, Folder 6-7)
      - Meetings and minutes 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 8-9)
      - Memoranda 1922-25 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - Reports and recommendations 1923-27 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Research proposals 1923-24, undated (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - Research in progress 1923-24 (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - Research data 1924-25 (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - Research results 1923-25 (Box 84, Folder 15-16)
      - Miscellaneous 1923-24, undated (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - National Women's Christian Temperance Union 1924 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - National Woman's Party 1933, [see also National Women's Trade Union League; U.S. Department of Labor--Women's Bureau] (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - National Women's Trade Union League, [see also Russell Sage Foundation-Employees' Representation-Worthington Pump & Machinery Company]
    - Articles and newspaper clippings 1921-43 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Boston affiliate 1929-33 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Conference and convention material 1922-26 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 85)
      - Elizabeth Christman 1921-37 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Mabel Leslie 1924-27 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Rose Schneidermann 1924-30 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Maud Swartz 1926 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Life and Labor Bulletin 1921-50 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - New Jersey affiliate 1941 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - New York affiliate
      - Correspondence 1928-46 (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - Meeting notices 1924-55 (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - New York Women's Trade Union League Bulletin, 1930-50 (Box 85, Folder 14)
      - Newspaper clippings 1941-45 (Box 85, Folder 15)
      - Reports 1921-49 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Pamphlets 1914-44, undated (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania affiliate 1928 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Protective legislation for women 1923-26 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Woman's Party conflict 1926 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - New Fabian Research Bureau 1935-37 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - New Frontiers in American Life Conference, Rochester, NY May 1940
    - General 1940 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper clippings 1940 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey Women's Trade Union League, [see National Women's Trade Union League] (Box 85)
  - New York Association of Unappointed Teachers 1934 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - New York Flower Mission 1897-1900, undated (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - New York School of Philanthropy
    - Coursework 1915-17 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Reports and memos 1915-16, undated (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - New York State Council for Legislative Action 1948 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - New York State Department of Labor 1938-48 (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Women's Trade Union League, [see National Women's Trade Union League] (Box 86)
  - Pennsylvania Conference on Labor Law Administration, [see Labor Law Administration Conference] (Box 86)
  - Pabst Postwar Employment Awards 1944 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Welfare Conference 1946 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Women's Trade Union League, [see National Women's Trade Union League] (Box 86)
  - Personnel Research Federation 1925-33 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Pictorial Review 1924-25 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Progressive Party
    - General 1948-49 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Women for Wallace 1948 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Foundation 1929-34, undated (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Russell Sage Foundation
    - General (Box 86)
      - Buildings 1921-42 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence
        - Clark, Earle 1916 (Box 86, Folder 11)
        - Glenn, John M., General Director 1910-37 (Box 86, Folder 12)
        - Harrison, Shelby M., General Director 1931-45 (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - Employees
        - Photographs of staffundated (Box 86, Folder 14)
        - Retirement plan 1922-26 (Box 86, Folder 15)
        - Salaries 1919-23, 1941 (Box 86, Folder 16)
        - Working conditions 1938-40 (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - History and organization 1938-42, 1982, undated (Box 86, Folder 18)
      - Library 1919-36, undated (Box 86, Folder 19)
      - Newspaper clippings 1916-45 (Box 86, Folder 20)
      - Publications, [see also SERIES III. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES]
        - Book reviews and advertisements 1916-56 (Box 86, Folder 21)
        - Catalogs 1942-57 (Box 86, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence 1924-40 (Box 86, Folder 23)
        - Distribution 1925-37 (Box 86, Folder 24)
        - Statistical Procedure of Public Employment Offices 1933-34 (Box 87, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous 1928-42, undated (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Research
        - Forms for data 1915-30 (Box 87, Folder 3)
        - Methods and problems 1926 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Women's Work, [see also SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES--Women's employment]
      - History and organization 1910-15 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda 1911-15 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Reports
        - To the advisory committee 1910 (Box 87, Folder 7)
        - Weekly 1911-12 (Box 87, Folder 8)
        - Monthly 1913-16 (Box 87, Folder 9)
        - Quarterly 1913-16 (Box 87, Folder 10)
        - Semi-annual 1914-15 (Box 87, Folder 11)
        - Annual 1911-15 (Box 87, Folder 12)
        - Individual 1916 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Department of Industrial Studies
      - History 1916-44 (Box 87, Folder 14-17)
      - Index of files 1948 (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - Memoranda 1912-48, undated (Box 88, Folder 1-30)
      - Programs of Work 1917-45 (Box 88, Folder 31)
      - Proposed investigations 1914-43 (Box 88, Folder 32-37)
      - Publications
        - General 1931-47 (Box 89, Folder 1)
        - Labor Agreements in the Coal Mines, by Louis Bloch 1931 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Publicity scrapbooks
        - Lists of 1960-61 (Box 89, Folder 3)
        - "The Coal Miner's Insecurity," 1922 (Box 89, Folder 4-7)
        - Sharing Management with the Workers1924-25
          - vols. 1-4 (Box 90, Folder 1-5)
          - vols. 5-6 (Box 91, Folder 1-3)
        - Employes' Representation in Coal Mines, 1925, vols. 9-10 (Box 91, Folder 4-5)
        - Employes' Representation in Steel Works, 1925, vols. 12-13 (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
        - Articles in journals 1925-26, vol. 14 (Box 92, Folder 3)
        - Labor publications 1925, vol. 15 (Box 92, Folder 4)
        - Book reviews1925-26
          - vol. 16, pt. 1 (Box 92, Folder 5)
          - vol. 16, pt. 2 (Box 93, Folder 1)
        - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company strike 1927 (Box 93, Folder 2)
        - Miners and Management 1934 (Box 93, Folder 3-4)
        - The Miner's Case and the Public Interest 1947-48 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Reports
        - Monthly 1918, 1926 (Box 93, Folder 6-7)
        - Quarterly 1917, 1927-28 (Box 93, Folder 8-10)
        - Semi-annual 1927 (Box 93, Folder 11)
        - Annual 1916-47 (Box 94, Folder 1-14)
      - Studies
        - Individual (Box 94)
          - 1910-26 (Box 95, Folder 1-17)
          - 1935-40 (Box 96, Folder 1-3)
        - Special projects
          - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company (Box 96)
            - District Conference 1916 (Box 96, Folder 4)
            - "Coal Miner's Representation," by Ben Selekman1920 (Box 96, Folder 5-7)
            - Reactions to the manuscript 1921, undated (Box 96, Folder 8-10)
            - "Employee Representation and the Worker," by Ben Selekman 1925 (Box 96, Folder 11)
            - Hearings at Crested Butte 1931 (Box 96, Folder 12)
          - Dutchess Bleachery
            - Employee records 1917-21 (Box 97, Folder 1)
            - Sharing Management with the Workers, [see also Publicity scrapbooks; SERIES VI. BOOKS FROM VAN KLEECK'S LIBRARY]
              - Articles and newspaper clippings 1924 (Box 97, Folder 2)
              - "A Labor Policy in Terms of Production," by Sadie Engel 1924 (Box 97, Folder 3)
              - Articles by RSF staff 1925, undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
          - Employees' representation, [ see also SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES-Coal; Labor]
            - "Employes' Participation in Management," by Ben Selekman 1919 (Box 97, Folder 5)
            - General 1919-34, undated (Box 97, Folder 6)
            - Articles 1920-30, undated (Box 97, Folder 7)
            - Correspondence 1921-29 (Box 98, Folder 1)
            - Memorandum 1921-28, undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
            - Newspaper clippings 1919-28 (Box 98, Folder 3)
            - A 1920-26, undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
            - American Cast Iron Pipe Company 1924-28 (Box 98, Folder 5)
            - American Multigraph Company 1919-21 (Box 98, Folder 6)
            - American Rolling Mills Company 1920 (Box 98, Folder 7)
            - American Telephone and Telegraph Company 1924-26 (Box 98, Folder 8)
            - American Woolen Company 1920-24 (Box 98, Folder 9)
            - Amoskeag Manufacturing Company 1924-28 (Box 98, Folder 10)
            - Armour and Company 1917-30, undated (Box 98, Folder 11)
            - B 1919-29 (Box 98, Folder 12)
            - Bank of Italy 1924-28, undated (Box 98, Folder 13)
            - Bethlehem Steel Corporation 1918-26, undated (Box 98, Folder 14)
            - Sidney Blumenthal and Company 1920-21 (Box 98, Folder 15)
            - Bridgeport Brass Company 1919-21 (Box 98, Folder 16)
            - Bridgeport Manufacturers 1919, undated (Box 98, Folder 17)
            - Brooklyn Rapid Transit Company 1921 (Box 98, Folder 18)
            - Browning Company 1919 (Box 98, Folder 19)
            - C 1920-26 (Box 98, Folder 20)
            - Cadbury Brothers 1925 (Box 98, Folder 21)
            - Cheney Brothers 1921-27 (Box 98, Folder 22)
            - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company 1925-33, [see also Special projects-Colorado Fuel and Iron Company] (Box 98, Folder 23)
            - Columbia Conserve Company 1925-30, undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
            - Corn Products Refining Company, IL 1920 (Box 99, Folder 2)
            - Lewis A. Crossett Company 1923 (Box 99, Folder 3)
            - D 1919-30 (Box 99, Folder 4)
            - Davis Coal and Coke Company 1922-25 (Box 99, Folder 5)
            - Deering, Milliken & Company 1921-24 (Box 99, Folder 6)
            - William Demuth & Company 1919, undated (Box 99, Folder 7)
            - Dennison Manufacturing Company 1920-25, undated (Box 99, Folder 8)
            - Henry A. Dix and Company 1922-25, undated (Box 99, Folder 9)
            - Dolphin Jute Mills, Paterson, NJ 1919-22, undated (Box 99, Folder 10)
            - Downey Shipbuilding Company 1919-20 (Box 99, Folder 11)
            - Dupont de Nemours & Company 1919-28, undated (Box 99, Folder 12)
            - Durham Hosiery Mills 1919-21 (Box 99, Folder 13)
            - Dutchess Manufacturing Companyundated (Box 99, Folder 14)
            - Eastman Kodak Company 1919-27 (Box 99, Folder 15)
            - Electric Trades Organization 1918-20 (Box 99, Folder 16)
            - Endicott Johnson Company 1919-24 (Box 99, Folder 17)
            - F 1928, undated (Box 99, Folder 18)
            - Ford Motor Company 1928-29, [see also SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES--Ford Motor Company] (Box 99, Folder 19)
            - G 1920 (Box 99, Folder 20)
            - General Electric Company
              - West Lynn, MA 1921-27 (Box 99, Folder 21)
              - Schenectady, NY 1926-27 (Box 99, Folder 22)
            - General Motors Company 1919-29 (Box 99, Folder 23)
            - Gibert & Barker Manufacturing Company 1918 (Box 99, Folder 24)
            - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company 1920, undated (Box 99, Folder 25)
            - H 1914-26 (Box 99, Folder 26)
            - Hano Renold, Ltd. 1919 (Box 99, Folder 27)
            - Hickey Freeman Company 1919-28 (Box 99, Folder 28)
            - Holt Manufacturing Company 1921 (Box 99, Folder 29)
            - I 1919-25 (Box 99, Folder 30)
            - Interborough Rapid Transit Company 1916, [see also SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES-- Labor--Unions] (Box 99, Folder 31)
            - International Harvester Company 1919-32 (Box 99, Folder 32)
            - Joseph and Feiss Company 1919-27 (Box 100, Folder 1)
            - K 1917-26, undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
            - L 1919-26 (Box 100, Folder 3)
            - Leeds Northrup Company 1918-28 (Box 100, Folder 4)
            - Louisville Varnish Company 1920-40, undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
            - M 1919-34 (Box 100, Folder 6)
            - Manning Paper Company 1922-30 (Box 100, Folder 7)
            - Midvale Steel and Ordnance Company 1918-19, undated (Box 100, Folder 8)
            - Mitten Management 1928-30, undated, [see also Philadelphia Rapid Transit Company] (Box 100, Folder 9)
            - Monarch Manufacturing Company 1921 (Box 100, Folder 10)
            - Morse Dry Dock and Repair Company 1919-20, undated (Box 100, Folder 11)
            - N 1919-25, undated (Box 100, Folder 12)
            - Nash Clothing Company 1921-28 (Box 100, Folder 13)
            - National Cash Register Company 1922-25, undated (Box 100, Folder 14)
            - O 1927 (Box 100, Folder 15)
            - P 1919-28 (Box 100, Folder 16)
            - Pennsylvania Railroad
              - General 1922-27 (Box 100, Folder 17)
              - Newspaper clippings 1921-25 (Box 100, Folder 18)
            - People's Gas, Light, and Coke Company 1920-21 (Box 100, Folder 19)
            - Philadelphia Plan 1919-21, undated (Box 100, Folder 20)
            - Philadelphia Rapid Transit Company 1919-29, [see also Mitten Management] (Box 101, Folder 1)
            - Plumb Plan 1919-22, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
            - Plymouth Cordage Company 1925 (Box 101, Folder 3)
            - Post Office Department 1920-22 (Box 101, Folder 4)
            - Proctor and Gamble 1918-29 (Box 101, Folder 5)
            - R 1920-34 (Box 101, Folder 6)
            - Rowntree Cocoa Works, England 1921-32, undated (Box 101, Folder 7)
            - S 1919-29 (Box 101, Folder 8)
            - Smith and Kaufman, Incorporated 1920-21 (Box 101, Folder 9)
            - Southern Metropolitan Gas Company 1926-27 (Box 101, Folder 10)
            - Sprague Electric Company 1919-21, undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
            - Standard Oil Company 1918-31, undated (Box 101, Folder 12)
            - Swift and Company 1923-28 (Box 101, Folder 13)
            - T 1919-23, undated (Box 102, Folder 1)
            - Tidewater Oil Company 1919-26 (Box 102, Folder 2)
            - U 1920 (Box 102, Folder 3)
            - U.S. Shipping Board 1918-1919, 1921 (Box 102, Folder 4)
            - United States Steel Corporation
              - General 1919-27 (Box 102, Folder 5)
              - Newspaper clippings 1924-26, undated (Box 102, Folder 6)
            - Virginia Bridge & Iron Company 1920 (Box 102, Folder 7)
            - Vulcan Iron Works 1920 (Box 102, Folder 8)
            - W 1921-26 (Box 102, Folder 9)
            - Walworth Manufacturing Company 1919 (Box 102, Folder 10)
            - Weinstock Lublin Company 1920 (Box 102, Folder 11)
            - Western Electric Company 1925-31 (Box 102, Folder 12)
            - Western Union Telegraph Company 1919-21 (Box 102, Folder 13)
            - Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Company 1920-27 (Box 102, Folder 14)
            - White Motor Company 1918-21, undated (Box 102, Folder 15)
            - Willys Overland Plant 1919-20 (Box 102, Folder 16)
            - Youngstown Sheet & Tube Company 1920-21, undated (Box 102, Folder 17)
            - Whitley Council 1918-19, undated (Box 102, Folder 18)
            - Worthington Pump & Machinery Company 1919-20, [see also National Women's Trade Union League] (Box 102, Folder 19)
          - Employment
            - Statistics 1928-31 (Box 102, Folder 20-28)
            - Hours of work 1919-33 (Box 102, Folder 29)
            - Insurance 1922-23 (Box 102, Folder 30-31)
          - Filene Store
            - Articles and news clippings 1919-30, 1957 (Box 103, Folder 1)
            - Correspondence
              - General 1919-31 (Box 103, Folder 2-4)
              - Filene, A. Lincoln 1922-31 (Box 103, Folder 5)
              - La Dame, Mary 1921-30 (Box 103, Folder 6)
            - Methods and plans 1921-29 (Box 103, Folder 7)
            - Negotiations 1921-29 (Box 103, Folder 8)
            - Research material 1924-29, undated (Box 103, Folder 9)
            - Filene-Kirstein case 1930 (Box 103, Folder 10)
            - "The Filene Study," 1925 (Box 103, Folder 11-13)
            - "Personnel and Management," 1926 (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
            - "Personnel and Management in a Retail Store," 1928 (Box 104, Folder 3-5)
            - "Afterword: Subsequent Developments and Their Significance," circa 1929 (Box 104, Folder 6)
            - Reactions to the manuscript 1929 (Box 104, Folder 7)
            - "The Filene Store: A Study in Employes' Relation to Management," 1930 (Box 104, Folder 8)
          - German Coal Industry
            - "Regularity of Employment in German Coal Mines," by Sadie Engel 1926 (Box 104, Folder 9)
            - "Conflict or Stability in the Bituminous Coal Industry," by Sadie Engel 1927 (Box 104, Folder 10)
            - Dr. Felix Hase's study 1933-38 (Box 104, Folder 11)
          - National Recovery Administration and Industry
            - Automobiles, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 104)
            - Hoisery, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 104)
            - Rubber, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 104)
            - Shipping, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 104)
            - Steel, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 104)
            - "Steel Workers Under the NRA," by Edward A. Wieck 1936 (Box 105, Folder 1)
            - Textiles, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 105)
            - Miscellaneous, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 105, Folder 2)
          - Rock Island Arsenal
            - Articles and news clippings 1919-22 (Box 105, Folder 3)
            - Organizational charts 1918-20 (Box 105, Folder 4)
            - Bulletins 1919-21 (Box 105, Folder 5)
            - Correspondence 1921 (Box 105, Folder 6)
            - Central Council 1919-21 (Box 105, Folder 7)
            - Joint Conference Committee 1920-21 (Box 105, Folder 8)
            - Production Committee 1920, undated (Box 105, Folder 9)
            - Rates of Pay Committee 1920 (Box 105, Folder 10)
            - Shop Expense Committee 1919-20 (Box 105, Folder 11)
            - Reports 1917-20, undated (Box 105, Folder 12)
            - Research notes 1920-21, undated (Box 105, Folder 13)
            - Reactions to Smith's manuscript 1921 (Box 105, Folder 14)
            - "The Works Council at Rock Island Arsenal," by Edwin S. Smith 1923 (Box 105, Folder 15)
          - Rocky Mountain Fuel Company
            - Articles and newspaper clippings 1928-33 (Box 105, Folder 16-18)
            - Contracts 1928-33, undated (Box 105, Folder 19)
            - People
              - Green, Jack 1931-33 (Box 105, Folder 20)
              - Peabody, J. Paul 1932-33 (Box 106, Folder 1)
              - Roche, Josephine 1928-46, [see also National Conference of Social Work; SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE] (Box 106, Folder 2)
              - Vincent, Merle 1931-36 (Box 106, Folder 3)
            - Reports 1930-34 (Box 106, Folder 4)
            - Research notes, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 106)
            - Statement of Operations 1928-31 (Box 106, Folder 5)
            - Statistics 1931-33, undated (Box 106, Folder 6)
          - Women in industry, [see also SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES--Women's employment]
            - List of published investigations since 1900, circa 1912 (Box 106, Folder 7)
            - Articles and news clippings
              - General 1921-45 (Box 106, Folder 8-9)
              - Hours 1921-31 (Box 106, Folder 10)
            - Clothing and accessories 1910-25, undated (Box 106, Folder 11)
            - Household workers 1919, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
            - Married 1924-31 (Box 106, Folder 13)
            - Other workers 1900, 1918, undated (Box 106, Folder 14)
            - Part-timeundated (Box 106, Folder 15)
            - Secretarial 1919, undated (Box 106, Folder 16)
            - Transportation 1918-26 (Box 106, Folder 17)
            - Connecticutundated (Box 106, Folder 18)
            - Delawareundated (Box 106, Folder 19)
            - Illinoisundated (Box 106, Folder 20)
            - Indiana 1900, 1910 (Box 106, Folder 21)
            - Massachusetts 1911-20 (Box 107, Folder 1)
            - Michigan 1911 (Box 107, Folder 2)
            - New Jersey 1912 (Box 107, Folder 3)
            - New York
              - General 1900, 1944, undated (Box 107, Folder 4)
              - Interviews, 60 Hour Factor Law 1905-06 (Box 107, Folder 5)
            - Ohio 1900, 1921, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
            - Pennsylvania 1900-28, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
            - Rhode Islandundated (Box 107, Folder 8)
            - Printed materials 1919-55, undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Smith College
    - Board of Trustees (Box 107)
      - Correspondence 1922-30 (Box 107, Folder 10-18)
      - Meetings 1922-29 (Box 107, Folder 19-21)
      - Committee on College Houses 1923-30 (Box 107, Folder 22)
      - Organization of college faculty 1925-27 (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous printed material 1912-57, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Training School for Social Work
      - Correspondence 1921 (Box 107, Folder 25)
      - Alumnae Committee (Box 107)
        - Correspondence 1922-26 (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
        - Minutes 1922 (Box 108, Folder 3)
        - Memoranda 1922-26 (Box 108, Folder 4)
        - Reports 1922-24 (Box 108, Folder 5-6)
      - Articles and news clippings 1922-23 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous material 1918-34 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Research Council 1927-45, undated (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Social Science Employees' Union 1940 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Social Workers for Smith 1928 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Social Workers' Alliance 1933 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Social Work Today 1941-42 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Society for the Advancement of Management
    - General 1938-56, undated (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Women's Work Conference 1944 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Taylor Society 1921-34 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Textile Workers' Union of America 1942-43 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - United Committee of South-Slavic Americans 1943-45 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America 1949-52, undated (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - United Nations 1942-45, [see also League of Nations] (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - United States Department of Labor, [see also SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES-Labor]
    - General 1920-40 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Committee to the Secretary of Labor 1933-34 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Perkins, Frances 1933-45, [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE] (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - United States Employment Service (Box 109)
      - Conference 1918 (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Federal Advisory Council (Box 109)